Stand up tall, reach out your hand.
Cut through the wind and make a stand.
The paint within brings
out a map of your own.
To the left and the right,
all we saw stormy nights.
All the rough winds and
waves coming day after day.
And the values we had
were about to collapse.
Oh, just where do we go next?
And as we look down to the compass in
hand Is it showing us the right direction?
All we know is nobody
here knows it for certain.
So close your eyes and breathe in deeply.
And listen to your soul.
You'll see a path in front of you.
And you'll know just where you need to go.
So stand up tall, reach out your hand.
Cut through the wind and make us stand.
Don't let the darkness
win, just break through.
I'll do it my own way,
that's what's best for me.
And you do it your way,
that's how it's got to be.
We're moving forward, now I'm ready.
But at times it's okay
to get help on the way.
For the future ahead, burning bright.
For what's ahead you see.
Is beyond your wildest dreams.
So stand up tall, reach out your hand.
Cut through the wind and make a stand.
Don't let the darkness
win, just break through.
We'll do it our way,
the best that we know.
With tears and doubts and tone,
we'll go where we all wanna go.
The page within brings colors of our own.
I can grab Kaido's clouds?
Of course I can!
We're both dragons, after all!
Even if I can't push it back,
Perhaps I can stop its advance.
Or even better, I can
change its direction.
This is my duty.
No one else can do it.
I must.
The capital will not be
destroyed under my watch.
As its rightful Shogun, I will guide
the land of Wano to a new dawn.
He shot beams from his eyes.
Don't tell me.
Is everyone alright?
I think we need to find a new spot.
Let us retreat further back.
Chi-chi's gone! What?
Did I lose him in the explosion?
There's no time to search.
We don't know when another might hit.
Maybe so.
I might die.
But I don't want to leave him here.
I'm sorry!
Awesome, I know!
Bet you know this one too!
Henry Queen!
Was that Niji's move?
You're catching onvin smoke.
Well, aren't you clever?
Ha ha, idiot.
Queen don't give it to you.
So, did I ace the test or what?
As you can tell, I did thorough
research on all of Jamba's.
I can replicate any move that your
brothers do, except not make it look good!
I don't care!
I cut ties with those jerks!
The idea was to show it to
you after you transformed,
but you really screwed that up for me!
Kicking your ass is one thing,
but I can't really stick it to
Judge unless I beat you in the suit!
That'd prove my superiority
beyond a shadow of a doubt!
I don't give a crap about
your dumb rivalries!
You know, I'm starting to
think that you don't like me!
We're Queen!
I think I nailed it right!
You've probably been on the
receiving end of that one before!
My beautiful arm!
All right, punk, it's on now!
What did I tell you?
Keep talking about those bastards
and this is what you get?
You telling me I gotta watch what
I say cause you're too sensitive!
Let me make one thing clear.
Suit or no suit you're going down!
I've got everything I need right here.
Let's end this.
Let's save.
Strike!
What makes you think
you have the upper hand?
Did you forget?
I sent your ass flying once
already and I can do it again.
It wasn't enough to win,
but I know that hurt.
We've been fighting for a long time.
You must be wearing down.
I'm ready.
Like it or not, I've
already accepted my fate.
I'm not the same guy you fought before.
Inferious Weakley!
You ain't never had a foe like me.
If you're not going to use it, I will.
Stealth blast!
You really can do it all, can't you?
Got you now.
Your back is wide open, smoke sloppily.
What?
How the hell did he disappear?
But he doesn't have to suit anymore.
He must be moving so fast
he's become invisible.
You'll run out of stamina soon enough.
Then he'll have to show himself.
Didn't think this one through, did you?
Get the hell out of here, rat.
Shoujou!
Thank goodness you're okay.
Let's go.
We have to hurry to a safe spot
before those two start fighting again.
Awesome-y!
That trap is still alive!
Damn it!
Now where did you run off to, Thinsmoke?
Could you help me?
Whoever you are!
Please, I have nothing to do with this!
I'm just a geisha from the capital!
Awesome man!
You're supposed to be in bed!
I came by asking for your services,
and they said you had a headache!
Well, you look nice and healthy
to me, you filthy little liar!
I try to be a good customer to
you, and this is what I get?
Rejection and deception?
You're getting too
cocky for your own good!
You were supposed to be my number
one girl now that Komurasaki is gone.
I won't forgive you.
You'll pay for lying to me and for
all those times you turned me down.
This is divine punishment.
I want to go home.
Your behavior required
swift and punitive action.
It's only natural justice has been served
You're not showing an ounce of remorse looks
like I need to punish you a second time
think about what you've
gained an exoskeleton muscle
strength and mobility more
tools in my arsenal that's
all if i fine-tune my
armament Haki and cover my
exoskeleton with it my legs
will become stronger than ever.
They'll be capable of supporting
even hotter flames than before.
This is Fire Chamba.
Faster acceleration, heavier weight.
I don't have any more doubt.
Don't you know that a man
should never hit a woman?
That's been a fact since
the age of dinosaurs.
I should have known, scumbag.
Of course it was you.
Call Yang Kong.
Where did Master Tweet
come from? Don't worry.
Just leave him to me. Okay.
There you are, Venge Smoke!
Now die!
That's cool!
Alarun!
Shumar Miftas!
Tendron! Blanche!
K! Warre! Jares!
No!
Now that has been smoke
power five ever three years!
But you're still trying to
deny the truth, Jeremiah boy?
You're the one in denial.
I'm my own man.
Repeating that crap doesn't make it true.
This dish still needs its final touch.
Dinosaur meat's tough, but
there's nothing I can't cook.
Let's finish this already.
Oh, shut up!
You're a failed cyborg and a failed human!
I won't lose to a
second-rate science project!
Now get lost, you asshole!
No!
Don't worry.
Your little friend is safe. Jaggy!
I'm so relieved.
Make sure you keep him safe.
I'll do my best.
Thank you so much.
Sanji was making some
of that rat food again.
And you take good care of her too, okay?
Your wound?
You're not still pleading, are you?
You should be.
Are you okay?
We need help!
Someone bring a first aid, kid!
Just remember, our mother selflessly gave
her life to protect you and your humanity.
That's why you're kinder
and more tender than anyone.
The battle in the pleasure hall of
the skull dome has come to an end.
The winner is Sanji.
I thought so.
Something happens when the
flames on his back go out.
He speeds up.
But his defense, on the
other hand, gets weaker.
He destroyed Master King's mask. Oh, man.
And it looks like the
rumors about him are true.
Black wings, white hair, brown skin.
If we tipped off the government, we'd
get a hundred million bear rebounding.
Hypothetically, that is
Imperial Flaming Wings.
The castle's already burning.
Give it a rest.
You gotta keep your cool and set an
example for your men, not set them on fire.
Why not step outside?
You seem a little tense.
That hundred million berry
thing really got to you, huh?
Hell of a bounty for intel.
What tribe are you from?
Why bother asking when
you're about to die?
Whatever his tribe is, it must be rare.
But that doesn't matter.
I have to find a way to beat him.
Dammit.
I'm running out of time.
But this goes on much longer.
A sword will kill me before he does.
You are far more
dangerous than I expected.
Yeah, same.
Your reign has gone on for long
enough, as tyrants end as pirates.
Step aside.
Rather arrogant, Arsha.
This is Kaido's destiny.
He will become the king of the pirates!
I'm sorry, but that dream ends here.
King of Hell!
Three-sword style!
Pugatory!
Onigiri!
You gave me this life.
I owe it to you.
Interesting.
I see why the world
government won't let you go.
You're a Lunarian, huh?
I saw your durability
test earlier. Impressive.
I'm getting out of this dump, and then
I'm going to start a new pirate crew.
What do you want to do, guinea pig?
I'm gonna turn this boring world upside
down if you want to come that's your choice
You think you can do it?
Change the world?
I'm the only one who can do it.
The test subjects are
escaping the facility.
Stop them at any cost! Roger that.
Taking this shot.
They aren't chasing us.
No, they sure aren't.
Open fire!
The bullets don't work.
What do we do?
No, no, no, no, no.
What the hell was that?
Nothing.
Oh, yeah.
I almost forgot to ask.
You got a name?
It's Albear.
Well, Albear, you're very strong.
From here on out, I'll call you King.
Fine with me.
You watch my back, and I'll watch yours.
I'll never sell you out.
You're my right-hand man to the end, King.
This world only has proof for one ruler!
The flames are burning.
I can't attack him.
Die, Ramen!
Imperial Flaming Wings!
What the hell was that? Magma?
It's a damned weapon!
These swords are treasures!
I'm not letting them go!
He's sped up. This is it.
I can cut him.
Burnt it!
See, you figured out my trick.
That's very clever of you.
You're damn right I did.
Now nothing can stop me from beating you.
Ahhhhhhh!
Ultra!
Take your trap!
Why are you trying to block me?
I thought you were invincible!
Or are you scared what
might attack my duty?
Oh, my God.
You are biologically
incapable of defeating me!
Blaming biologists is a weak excuse.
I won't limit myself like that.
I shall remember you for your brave
resorts, or your arrogance, I should say.
I'll carve it into your memory myself!
Do I seriously doubt
you'll live through this?
Imperial Bellamy Frames!
Oh, my God.
King of Hell, Three-Sword Serpents!
One hundred and three mercies!
This is the end for you, Rorodawa!
Dragon damnation!
Ah, Kaido...
I...
You still holding on to that, Dream King?
You really think I'm Joy Boy?
I mean, I'm not complaining here.
But are you sure the world I'm looking
to make is the one that you want?
Well, a legend is just a legend.
And I could never ask for
more than you've given me.
I'm alive because of you.
My life is yours.
So you must remain undefeated.
and I will do the same.
You will be king of the pirates.
I know that you need nothing less than
the greatest swordsman in the world.
So until the day comes
when I defeat him and take
his title I promise you
that I will never lose.
Again is that okay King of the Pirates?
I will become
the king of hell.
The Battle of the Ritebring Tower outside
the Skull Dome has come to an end.
The winner, Zoro.
Thank you.